Heat.
Hey, Heat.
Heat. Heat. N.
Heat. Heat.
Heat. Hey, Heat.
Am
I audible?
Hello. Hello.
was coming now.
I hope I am audible.
Yeah. Uh for those who are tuning in, I
am kind of late to start the stream. So
uh
I don't know if I'm over here.
Hope I am live, bro.
Mh.
I'm literally on my cycle. I'm so late.
I'm so late.
Okay.
Am I live? Really? Okay, I'm live. Okay.
Okay. Good. Good. Good. Good. So, uh
two things. Uh
it is it is going to be sunset. I'm
still in the road out here in the road.
Cycle is here. Uh
I'll be going to the school area.
I'm almost near my school area. I as I
need to go to a certain spot. I will
park my cycle uh on the school uh
parking area and I'll um
and I'll uh show you guys some moments.
I I know a good spot.
Uh even though sun is setting, even
though it's going to be 5:30, the sunset
was at like 5:18
p.m.
It's so windy out here. It is super
windy.
So
yeah,
I I initially wanted to mount my phone
on the cycle and give you like me riding
the cycle view.
But I don't think I can do that today
cuz I don't have a phone holder anymore.
The old one got stolen, right? And this
is a new cycle. So I have to buy a new
one. Oh yeah. I have to be careful.
Shouldn't hold my phone or get caught by
the call police.
Hello.
God, that's a good block.
I want to cross the door.
I don't think I can close any
for those tuning in. Hello. I'm not
Hello, welcome. My name is Joc.
I'm a constellation YouTuber.
I'm currently crossing a road.
It's about to get night. Oh god.
It's about to get high.
>> What's the better choice?
I think the better choice is this.
I think I'll cross this way.
M. Sorry. So, so, so, sorry. Long scene.
Uh you were seeing my uh desktop
that was not the scene I wanted to show
you guys
accidentally.
I think I need to lock my
uh screen for a bit
closing as you can see.
Okay, we still haven't lost the sunset,
so don't worry. I'm going to give you
guys the sunset. We're coming here for
it. Even though I'm a bit late, but I
got you guys
or my teachers or somewhere.
It's fine. They're all working.
I believe I can still park even if it's
late. Just needing the back.
Okay,
I'm here.
need this.
It's like ASMR.
Okay, I'm I'm ready.
Okay. Okay.
Who's here? What is What is that doing?
Oh god, there's a teacher. I know.
Uh she she think oh there's a teacher
right now. I just talked to her earlier
yesterday.
I'm going to wait for the crossing and
she will not listen.
I just hope she doesn't say my her name.
She posted by my real name.
Oh god.
Yeah, she's talking with another
teacher.
Is it not too late already? Uh, it's too
late.
I can still show you the uh this thing.
It's still sunset. I'm going to go down
into the water.
I will make
I will make it. So, don't worry.
Oh god.
What the
I thought some bad people could they
might see me.
Oh god. So we're going to this area over
here.
I don't want other people to see me cuz
I'll get scolded. Why are you here?
So yeah, this is a place I recently
discovered.
And there's like an ocean after behind
that area. So I have to like I think
there I can cross here. But the
no one usually comes here. So yeah,
if someone is here, uh, that's going to
be awkward awkward.
Even though the sunset is over, I just
wanted to sit by the riverbed
and talk and stuff.
Well, this is this is this is that area.
There's no one here.
I'm under the bridge, bro. I'm under the
bridge.
There's like graffitis and stuff.
Um, what the
I I changed the thing. Uh, you need to
make a feature to lock the sliders. By
the way, uh, you're a jam. Look at that.
There's so many rocks and stuff. Got to
be careful. And there's no one here at
this point.
Uh I hope I don't I'm not interrupting
someone if they're doing something sussy
over here uh behind this area cuz so far
there's no much people.
I have to get out of here before it's
late late because um
you know if it's dark it's dangerous and
scary.
Yeah. This is the spot.
No one's here. I can I can I have this
for all to myself.
Yeah. Look at this area, bro. Komina.
Isn't just
very windy.
And look at this. All the rocks are uh
covered with like metal wires so they
don't uh move uh move out of place and
stuff.
This is such a good spot.
This is underneath the bridge.
Hello, Goji boy. Welcome.
Thank you for those who are coming in,
tuning in. So, we got to sit in one of
the rocks over there and just chill.
Of course, my pants are going to get
dirty.
Ah, nice job. I have to be careful. It's
kind of slippery here.
Oh lord,
I'm I'm onehanding, bro.
Oh that's slippy. Slippy.
Oh my god.
Oh my god. Oh
Oh Oh my god. Okay.
Oh Okay.
It's so good.
Where's the sun? Uh sun is setting
behind this thing.
But it's so nice place, right?
Very windy. I hope the internet is fine
here because uh my uh the internet is
kind of bad when I come here.
So yeah, very windy.
So now Oh god, it's so windy.
Look, is that a bat?
That's a bat.
It's coming out of his shell.
That's a small bat.
He flew away.
Yeah, this is one of the spots I
recently discovered.
I'm just going to sit on this rock and
we're going to chill out here. Make sure
Oh Make sure I do not get my uh
shoes wet.
Is that
crow poop? Bird poop.
It's not recent. The show.
Uh it it is recent.
There's a cigarette butt. I'll use that
to clean it. Oh god.
What the heck?
Ah I don't want it to be on my
pants.
Ah.
Never expected myself to clean chrome
like bird poop with cigarette butts and
like someone's thrown cigarette butts.
Wow.
Ah, yeah. Like,
hi. I can sit.
I did bring some snacks.
Oh I forgot
to bring the bread.
Wait, I think I did. M.
What is bro doing?
I'm here.
So,
Uh m I'll just blur
Mina
M.
Did I bring the
I forgot to bring bring the bread, bro.
I was wanting to eat it.
I forgot the bread thingy.
No, I do have monster.
A white monster coin.
I do have white monster coin.
Uh what the
I do have white monster coin. So yeah
trip on
this is a tripod I use.
This is a tripod I use.
I have no idea how I'm going to use this
while holding a power bank,
but yeah.
Oh god, how do I open this?
Hey,
what's the other way?
I forgot you don't need to put it
horizontally.
Hi.
Okay. Tripod moment.
But how will you hear me? I forgot to
take my external mic. Ah. Yada. I
forgot. No,
I forgot.
I actually forgot.
How will I keep you? Where will I keep
you guys?
Can you hear me?
has ah
hello artificial welcome.
Hola
from kid. Hello. Hello.
It's getting night time right now.
It is night time.
I don't know what I'm doing. I I wanted
to just come here, do a stream, see the
sunset and stuff, drink a can of Monster
Energy
while eating bread. But I forgot to take
my bread.
Uh, no. Measure energy ultra.
So, how's everyone doing?
And
that is so windy. Wait, let me try noise
operation.
Tell me how good and bad it is. Okay.
Uh my suppression can you hear me?
Is it audible? Is it too much
damn box?
It's so cool that there's light
underneath me.
So, you can literally see who's down
here. If they if people from over there,
if people from over there were to If
people from over there were to see me,
they would be like, "What is this person
doing?"
Okay,
my dad just came home. Welcome back.
Welcome back.
How you guys doing everyone? How was
your day?
Uh, and everything.
I do have this guy
It's an apple juice. I only have some
some of it as you can see. Only a little
bit.
I think the stadium stadium is running
probably like cl like club activities or
something. So they use the stadium over
there. The one over there. Can you see
that?
But it
that's a stadium over there.
I wish I can take you guys on a night
night cycling.
If I for that I need to make sure my
equipment stays upright and it does not
move around and stuff.
If it falls off now I'm dead dead.
But it is so nice that you know this is
such a good spot. You can just chillax.
You're free from all the from your
worries and
all these responsibilities and
everything. You just here to just chill
and wipe. And I feel like that's a big
thing honestly.
Maya, let me give you some ASMR
show.
So, I'll stay here for 10 more minutes
and we'll move. Okay,
let's see if I can take you guys on a
cycling ride.
If that is possible, let's go outside.
So, for a while, okay, as long as I can.
The thing the issue right now with the
show is I forgot to take my external mic
one uh mic. But,
uh the best way I can talk to you guys
is what do you call it? I can put like a
scene where I'm it says I'm literally
cycle I cycling. I cannot speak much.
And then uh once I've stopped my cycle,
I can take you guys for a walk or
something,
move around and stuff. I can do that
probably.
So done it. Let me know, okay,
if that's what you guys would want for
today. But yeah, we just chill or today
we just chilling and
today we just chilling.
I forgot to take my mic rock vaka. I
took everything. I took extra power
bank, extra charger, uh USB cable,
everything. I forgot to take my external
light.
What country are you in? Japan. I'm
currently in Japan as a language
exchange student.
I'm here as a
a language student.
Uh I'm in Japan.
Yeah, I'm in Japan.
the land of the rising sun
and it's 6:00 p.m. and it's already
night.
Oh god, it's actually night. It's
getting darker, isn't it? It is getting
dark here. The sun has seted right now,
everyone. The sun has seted.
God, and it's so windy and cold, too.
You can see the temperature on my screen
on my on top of my head. It says 19° 19°
C. It is cold. And on top of that,
windy.
Honto.
Oh, bats. Oh, god. Bats. Oh, bats. Oh,
bats. Oh, god.
Batman is here.
Ah, so many bats are here. Oh god, my my
camera is not that good.
My uh bats are not nearby.
I just wish I'm audable
like that.
Pretty
awesome.
Holy
wind.
Okay.
Hi.
Okay. Uh the
the can is empty. We are done with the
Monster Energy drink.
It's really getting later. Uh so 5 more
minutes and we'll depart from here.
Okay. I have to take the trash with me.
Cannot trash this beautiful place. Uh so
I have to take it with me.
So now we have we have to be a
responsible person.
So yeah. Yeah.
Will that leak?
There's a cycling area over there. I
can't take you guys on a cycling thing
area
for a while, I guess.
Uh maybe we can explore the stadium
area. There's a park over there
to uh Wakan. I don't know.
Uh yeah, I could. So, I don't know.
Okay, 66%age. Uh, I have to put put my
power bank
and hold
93 percentage charge on my power bank.
So, it can last for a while. Okay, we
can depart. It's 55 minutes.
survive.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh
to be careful doc mix
it's I think this is limestone or
something. It's like it has a yellowish
color.
Also a new feature I forgot to show you
guys on stream. There's a new feature
though. I can now draw on screen.
I may draw a sign.
I can I can draw a sign.
There's a sun now
for those who are visiting the stream.
Uh yeah, it's a sun
go in there.
But yeah, uh we'll come here in the
morning someday on Saturday maybe. Uh if
looking at the weather and stuff, we'll
go for a longer journey and stuff
someday. Not today. Uh today I think I
can if possible if I can put myself uh
put my put you guys on my cycle
with the with
Oh god. I'm I'm I'm I'm gassing out from
my mouth. Oh my god. Oh god.
Oh Oh I need something
whole. Oh god.
Oh boy. Oh Oh Oh Oh
Yeah, but Oh my god. Ah. Ah, one handing
is hard.
I think I'm the only one. No, no, there
are a lot of girls on YouTube and Twitch
right now.
Uh, you're on kick, right? Yeah, don't
worry.
Oh, wait. I can't see anything. What the
h?
Okay.
Oh god. It's This is why I said I have
to leave quickly
even if it's for a short while cuz it's
so dark over here.
It is super dark.
Oh yeah. But this gives me a vibe that
I'm literally near the ocean cuz the
sand there's sand and stuff and that is
rare. I have to climb on top of that
area.
Oh god. No, I don't need to climb the
staircases. Yeah, I have to make sure no
one sees me cuz if they're seeing me,
they will start questioning why did you
go here? It's a restricted area.
this and that.
So be extra careful.
Thank you for following.
Wait, where did you follow?
Oh, thank you for following on kick.
Thank you so much. I I barely have any
kick viewers,
but yeah, but I always multiream to kick
regardless.
So yeah, thank you again.
Uh I have to make sure no one Oh god,
I have a I have a crazy
I I have a I think there's a chance I
might see my teachers.
There is a chance that I might see my
teachers. I just hope I don't walk cuz I
parked my cycle there.
So, it is
if they ask me, I'll just mute the mic.
And if they ask me, I'll just mute the
mic and just make some excuse. Oh, wait.
They'll see my tripod.
So, I can't lie.
They'll see my tripod though.
So,
for a bit.
It's supposed to.
Oh god. I will not show you my school.
So don't worry.
How much product
to take the cycle from this place and
get get the hell out of here before
anyone sees me.
But it's so nice though.
It's so nice though. Yeah. With the
power of blur, you cannot see anything.
It is nice. Oh yeah. You guys couldn't
see my cycle last time, right? So, this
is my cycle, by the way.
This was my cycle.
Oh, what the
This is the new cycle I bought. The tire
is like thicker.
So, this is a new cycle I bought.
Okay, I'll blur it. I'll see if I can
put you on here.
If it's possible, then we are good and
lucky.
It's possible.
They'll be shaking though
if I put it like this.
That'll be shaking. But this is a view,
right?
The power bank will go around, but it's
fine. I can put it underneath here.
Okay.
Okay. Can is it is this stable?
One second.
Okay.
What the is there any How do I read
comments, bro?
The thing is I cannot read comments no
matter what I do. Are you in that ghost
that wonders the Japanese streets at
night? No, I literally my school. I went
to show you guys the sunset
under the bridge which is a restricted
area.
Yeah, let's go cycling. Okay. Uh, let me
know if the footage is shaky or not.
Oh god.
Oh, this could work.
Minda, this actually could work.
This actually could work.
Wait, this actually could work.
Okay, I won't be able to read chat, but
then we'll enjoy the cycling thingy.
Wait, not there. I'll just have to put a
text search light.
All
right.
Okay,
that should do it.
Okay, if the stream dies, do let me know
in chat. Okay, I hope that I I was able
saying saying that. Okay. Company.
That is
heat.
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
Oh god, this phone is shaking so much.
I really need a shock clover kind of
tripod or something. Stabilizer man.
This is so bad.
This is the ramen shop. I always go for
eating ramen. It's really cheap over
here.
Okay, that is not
Okay, let's stop for now.
We can make out the cars, walls, and
buildings.
Hello.
Uh,
what?
Uh I'm
sorry.
Uhoh.
I'll do 800.
I'll make it bigger.
Okay. Is this good? Is this good? I
think that's good. Okay, I'm going to
lock it again and put it back.
What the heck?
We'll go through the cycling area.
There's a long cycling area. So, we're
going to go through that. Okay.
It's on the left. So, that's literally
the area I was under bridge. This is the
bridge I was under. Oh,
Oh
Okay, this is a good spot.
Uh
I was underneath this bridge
uh over here.
I was underneath there. Sitting sitting
over there. Then we are here.
Uh
why is it shaking so badly? Because I'm
on a cycle
and uh
and my only thing is like this. I put
the thing like this and the power bank
will be like over there. I don't know.
It's shaking a lot. So it will be like
that. Uh I don't have a I don't have a
phone stand.
Do you speak Spanish if it's little?
Even if it's little. No, I speak
English.
I speak English and I know Japanese.
I can't read. I can speak a little bit.
Also, Mina, look at the lights.
Look at Ah, it's so grainy. But it's the
lights are amazing.
Wait, when did when did Urchan add like
stabilizer? Oh, wait. This automatic
mp twilight white balance automatic.
Hey, when did you add exposure and
stuff? What the hell?
I was just asking. Uh, don't me. No, no,
no, no. Go. I was not angry at you
though.
I'm not angry at you.
Uh, okay. Let me put this guy back here.
I'm not angry at you for anyone. Don't
worry. I just hope I don't dox myself.
Uh,
okay.
Will this
This is where Oh
Okay, Mina, I'm going to I'm going to
cycle again. So, I won't be able to
recharge comments again.
So, yeah. Back to
back. Oh, wait. It can fall off like
this, man.
For sure.
But yeah, the area we're going to go,
it's like cycling area.
88%.
Okay.
It's my first time exploring this area.
By the way,
it might seem horrory, but
I actually don't know where I'm going,
but it's
Oh god, it's so hot.
Oh god, it's so early.
Oh my god.
What is this area?
Oh It's so dark.
Wait, this is so dark.
What the I have to turn on flash.
It's so Oh my god, it's so dark.
What the
is it so dark
there?
Uh I cannot read chat by the way.
Those students were looking at me
awkwardly.
Stabilizer is better at it. I did my
good job then. But this side is kind of
the left side is can be shaky. I have to
move it to the other side. Maybe. Should
I do that right now?
I could do that.
It's so weird being here.
M.
I can actually adjust this.
God, I'm in a middle of nowhere
and it's so scary.
H
So what I can do is
move it this way to the left area.
Left most area
that will be better.
So it's more stable. It won't as long
Yeah. This will be better. Yeah. So so
so this is better. It's more stable.
This is more stable. I
feel like this is more stable.
Yeah. This is more stable. I feel like
if you see any ghost, clip it in chat.
Okay. Clip it. Okay. here. Uh
oh, it's not.
Oh, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What the How do I make it upward?
Or should I just go this way?
Uh, that's upside down.
But wait, let me cook.
But what if I tighten this?
No, this will put more weight though.
My
Oh. Oh I almost docked myself.
Okay. Oh,
what if I do it like this then?
Okay, let's test this.
Uh
what the
I have to put the
power bank
charging. Okay, this should work. Huh?
Why is it fast charging? I need super
fast.
Hey,
who needs fast charging in 2026? I need
super fast charging.
Hey, why is it like that? Wait, what did
I do? What the hell?
No. Give me super fast.
This phone cannot survive without super
fast. The deal. Oh my god.
Hey,
please, please, please, please. What did
I do, bro?
Bro.
Okay, fine. it.
This is a cool area by the way. First
time already coming over here. It's so
horri.
It's like a tunnel.
This one's car.
Is it watchable? Is it viewable? Is it
okay?
Is it okay? Okay.
But the focus is bad.
Aland.
How come the focus is bad?
Okay, it.
Okay, that should do it.
Oh I I didn't bring any water.
No, I have a bottle so I can make my
car.
Uh,
how am I supposed to go this Okay.
Dope is like dog. Okay. This way.
Come under.
Why is it still say outside mode? What
the
Stop spamming it.
No wonder you're outside mode.
outside mode. Samsung,
I know I'm outside. I'm in the middle of
nowhere
and
God knows where I am. I'm in my cycle
exploring.
I just hope.
Bro, does anyone know where Oh my god.
What is that?
Wait, where am I?
I'm just cycling. I don't know where am
I. What the hell?
Yeah, I'm going to take the main road
and I go back home.
I'll lower my gear. It's harder to kind
of
psycho.
Oh god.
That was a lady
smoking a cigarette over there
nearby to the
and she's allowed. I smiled a bit. I
don't know if she could make me out. I
don't have my expression.
But I was in good
That's
great.
60ulate
the forest
the forest.
Not again.
Is it going to like this?
There's a traffic
there. Okay. Sorry. Okay.
I think there is one.
Wait, is this the
where they did the fireworks?
I think it is the area.
Sorry.
Oh, wait. This is a football field.
Oh Careful.
I think
we're exploding again. Oh, and the
dragon.
It just it just hit me in my mouth. What
the heck?
It's a narrow road.
I can even see the road.
It's so
cyber.
I got
I reached in
flight.
somebody
and it's dangerous
for this
light
working.
It's uh
okay, there you go.
This is
the spot.
Oh, what the
light over here. So, I'm going reach
that
I'll reach out. Okay.
Uh, not
trans.
Uh,
nothing.
Oh, there's something going on over
there.
It's record.
Uh, my internet is a bit odd.
A lot of cyclists are here
to go.
The place I'm going, if I'm correct, I
was not able to stream from there
because of the lack of signal.
So that's something I should be very off
m
I'll put you guys back. Okay.
I have an idea
my stream
it's going to die. Let me know.
Okay.
Heat up
here.
It is really nice to cycle like this.
Honestly,
I'm literally
This is like a ocean.
No, wait. I can get off here. Nothing.
It's dark. I should not
It's a guy.
What is this sign?
Oh, cars cannot go past this area. Okay,
bro. Where the am I am I? I'm sorry
for sweating, but this is creeping me
out.
Where am I even going?
I wish it was morning.
So many bugs are hitting my face.
Something moved in the bushes. What the
Hey, maybe speed up.
I think I'm 7 kilometers away from home.
Oh
Does this go on forever?
Or is that light?
Okay.
I should become a
like
a streamer or something at this point.
I'm cycling in dark areas at night.
Crazy.
I mean this is some sort of pond right
in some way.
Okay. I can see light. I think we are
getting to a city area or town area.
I think.
Yeah.
Should I
Should I go through the
Look at that. That's a bridge.
I think I had to go up this way.
Okay, we going through this area again.
Oh god, I don't know where I am. how
much far I am
but I feel like I might reach to the
right other side of the riverbed
if I'm correct. Did you see that? There
are people jogging in this night.
Literal darkness.
How and why and why?
I just saw three people now.
One one came for walking his dog. See my
dog.
I don't know. Should I go this way?
That's scary area.
That is scary. Should I go this way?
Not bad. Let me check my Google maps.
You're going to end up in Japanese
horror. Um, your signal is so bad.
Hey, Hunto,
let me check
where I am.
I feel like I'm so far everywhere.
I'm in a golf ground.
What the hell?
Uh,
I'm just going to go there now.
Oh my god, I'm in a different area.
What the hell?
I'm that far out.
Uh,
so I'm like how many kilometers away
from home?
I believe I'm
7 kilometers.
Why am I coming?
Uh if I'm going this way
uh
what I can do is go straight and go to
the
uh try to get on the bridge.
Ohashi bridge.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
By the way, let me actually do a
a Google map thingy.
You got lost? Yep. I I am lost.
Okay.
Can you see the thing?
Uh, okay.
Okay.
Come now.
How about that?
Have to take a emergency idle meeting
leak. One second. Let me mute my mic so
you don't hear me take
Heat. Heat.
Hello. Hello. Hello.
That's not bad.
Let's go.
Okay, let's go. We are so far away from
home.
Okay,
I won't be able to reach since I'm
cycling.
Honestly though, in the future now, I
should buy like a GoPro action camera or
something so it's e better to
better and simpler to look at, right?
Saw that in there.
Did I leak? Did I? Did
I Did I expose my face?
Oh
Wait. Did something happen? Oh god.
Uh.
Jo, go.
Sorry. Sorry.
Oh my god. This tripod.
I don't see anything, right?
I have to explore that out. What time
was it? 6:54.
Okay. 654. Remember that.
What again?
What the is going on?
Stupid foreigner.
N. What? How is it?
How is it happening?
for the second time,
bro.
Oh my god.
How and why?
Don't you dare do that,
please.
How is it moving away?
Is it because I put height?
Okay. Wait.
Wait. Let me tighten the screw. Okay.
Let me go. Not there.
Is it clear? Okay. I think it's clearer.
You'll see the basket, but it's fine.
I swear if it does it again, I'm going
to crash out.
Wait, it says to go left.
What?
My Google Maps is saying go straight.
Oh, yeah. Okay,
I'll go back now.
Ah, it happens.
That's
There's another cycle coming. Incoming.
That was a pedestrian motorcycle.
My bad. How do I make it not look at the
focus on the
How do I make it so it doesn't focus on
the basket?
I want it to focus on the
Okay.
So I have to turn a I have to take a U
turn.
That's why Google Maps is saying so I
can get on the bridge which we just
crossed underneath in the cycling path.
Uh so I believe I'm 7.5
kilometers away from my home.
So yeah, you have to take the this left
right. Okay. If I go any further, I
think I won't reach home anytime soon.
So,
we'll have to take a right
from here.
Is it?
Or I can go there on top.
Is there an area here?
Oh god, it's scary.
Uh,
should I trust Google Maps? Oh god, it's
a bumpy road though. Oh
it is a bumpy road.
Oh god, I'm okay.
camera for my phone.
Oh god, it's off road time.
Off road time.
Is this even the right area?
It's so bumpy though.
Wait, the road is closed.
I'm hearing weird noises.
What the Where am I?
Oh Where am I?
I have to walk it off or something.
Wait, what is this area,
bro? What is that
Where am I?
The
Uh,
okay. I think I'm supposed to go
downhill, but that's a steep road.
I might fall, though.
What the hell?
Oh
Slowly
cutie.
I think there are people here.
It's just 700 p.m.
Is this a construction area?
How am I going to get up on the
bridge this way?
I'm lost again.
you, Google Maps.
This stupid thing
is so dumb.
Where am I? And how do I go?
Why ride at this time? It was morning.
Uh, how do I go back?
Where the am I? Oh my god.
It told me to get on this bridge.
But I'm in this middle of nowhere. I'm
in a construction site. I should have
taken the other way around.
I have to go back.
Okay, I'll take
I think some I can feel something on my
back. What the hell?
Uh,
okay.
How did you get even low? I was
I don't know.
I went straight.
Put phone always falling. I want to kill
every someone right now.
I'm cursing a lot. Sorry. Uh I ended up
exploring a place I was not I never
prepared
and I ended up getting lost.
God dang it.
And it's night. I don't even have a
cycling gear like protective light.
This and that.
Why did I There you go. Why did I even
trust Google Maps?
Google Maps, you're bucka.
Oh, this terrain is so bad.
I have to wash my tires tomorrow.
Tonight for tomorrow.
The fact that I don't even have water
with me. It's so pain.
I'm so thirsty, too.
Like, I think I can go this way to get
out.
Get up the mountain.
I cannot.
It's uphill,
bro. This is so scary.
Not going to lie.
I just want to see the street.
I don't want to be here. Why the is
saying
arrived when it's not arrived?
How do I get out of here?
Okay, I think
I think I have an idea.
We'll have to cycle again
through there.
If my stream dies, do let me know
ASAP.
I have an idea. I'm going to trust my
gut.
I'm glad I did not climb that mountain
area.
Oh god, that uphill was nasty though.
I should just stick to the cycling
lights.
There's a bridge up.
No, it's a river. So, it's a
Yeah, small bridge probably.
So, I wanted to connect to the road,
right? Ah,
stupid phone.
I think I'm supposed to go that way.
What the
Okay. Okay, this should do it.
Uh,
how's my
Path of darkness.
So
ah sorry
wrong scene.
I hope I'm supposed to go That's
this is someone's house.
But I see a road.
I can finally see a road,
guys.
I see you.
I see the road.
Oh my god. But I'm not lost anymore.
I'm in some kind of fear
right now.
I think I'm supposed to go this way.
Yes.
This wasn't
the sky.
The night sky is so beautiful, man. It's
so beautiful.
The light
is so
Where should
I get to the bridge though?
river this way.
So you get on the main road.
There is a vending machine here
broke.
So I cannot buy anything.
Okay.
Okay, they're going
over.
My leg is
again
There's a car.
Okay, guys. Supposed to go right if I'm
correct.
That's a bridge.
I suppose
that is a path.
Uh
I'm 10 kilometers.
Can I not go this way?
I could.
Uh,
I can't.
I want to go this way.
Okay.
I think I'm in a highway right there.
But the question really is, can I go
through this area?
I see a staircase. Can I not take I
don't
there.
Uh, can I not take it up
and then go through this video.
I think I can.
Oh, let me go to my chat.
Oh, wait. You're looking at a bow. Oh,
yeah. You can see it. Okay.
Oh, god.
Thank God they have looking
areas like this
helps.
Oh my god.
Uh there is a po chance that I might
have to restart my stream cuz my phone
now it's not charging
on super fast charge. So I might have to
restart the streaming now. So, I said,
"Oh, hold on tight till I restart."
Holy God, we finally made it to a
highway.
Uh,
give me a minute.
Oh,
yeah. The moon looks so beautiful. Look
at this area.
So beautiful.
It's so cool.
So cool.
Have you ever played Pokemon? I
haven't played much of Pokemon.
Actually, I've played Pokémon Go once.
That's about it.
Also, people, I'll I'll I'll end the
stream. Not end the stream. I'll restart
the stream. Okay. I have to make sure my
phone can charge in super fast charging.
Uh if it doesn't charge and it's bad. It
is bad. If it cannot charge on super
fast charging, it is bad. Uh I want to
last longer for this stream. So yeah,
I'll be back. Okay, we are we are qu
I'll just uh end the stream for a little
bit. Okay,
we're not fully stopping. You'll see a
waiting screen. So yeah, how many
kilometers to go? We are we have to go
back 10 kilometers back home.
So yeah, 10 km.
This became a cycling stream. This
became like a
Okay, we should be back online.
I just had to close the app. It fixed
itself.
That is good.
We're live again.
Uh
Oh, 10 kilometers. Oh my god.
Okay. Uh, I'll be back. Is my stream
live again?
Can someone hear me? Let me know. Please
tell me in chat if I'm live.
Hello. Hello.
Uh, do let me know in chat if I'm live.
Okay, I'm live. Okay.
Oh, you are okay. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
I think I can turn off the flash. Maybe
I'll turn off the flash. It's eating a
lot of um corn. Oh, flash is off. Never
mind.
Oh my god.
I ended up doing a field test.
I didn't expect I'll do this kind of
streaming today, but
today was something like
Okay, let's go.
Uh,
back to cycling for 10 kilometers. Back
home.
hell. Again.
Ah.
The amount of time I am going crazy is
insane. I'm going to go crazy, bro. I am
literally going crazy
if it falls off again.
Oh my god. I'm going to go crazy.
Heat.
Oh, the night is so beautiful.
Wow.
Heat. Heat.
What is this downhill?
There's like uh tennis court and stuff.
Can you see it?
Uh there's like tennis court and stuff.
Can you see it? I cannot uh change the
position.
So that's why sorry now
the people playing tennis
Now, how do I get on top of the highway?
I just I think I just have to follow
this route
probably.
It's a junction.
Uh
Wait,
would this Google say again?
Uh,
how do I
I need to cross one more bridge, right?
So,
I think I'm supposed to go straight
and then from the next intersection I go
right
Maybe
that's the ST the upper head, right?
Okay.
I think it's fine.
Uh, is there a cycle?
Uh,
I think there is.
Is this a cycle park?
No. Wait. Looks suspicious.
Uh,
what is this?
I like this.
Okay. See? Oh, this way. Okay.
Oh, this way works. Okay, got it.
Oh, don't me.
Another
20 minutes.
What time is it? 7:34.
Wait, let's go.
Heat.
Okay, in 20 minutes in 20 minutes we'll
be home.
So yeah,
I never seen this area. This is my first
time seeing this area.
I can see pedestrians now.
I should be in that other side.
Actually,
let me switch lanes.
Is that a supermarket?
Oh, that's a medical shop.
Ah store is here.
Wait, I think I reached the area event
yesterday.
Wait, what the is it the same area?
Wait, I think it's a different area.
Uh,
I I I feel
like I've seen some of these. Maybe this
is a different area.
Don't know.
If I had money, bro, I would have taken
you guys to a ramen restaurant and I
would have filmed myself eating.
Next time. There's always a next time.
Remember,
the outdoor streams are like an
adventure. Oh my god. Almost hit that
same board. The outdoor streams are like
a
Wait, I reached Daiso. What?
M I just reached Daiso. Wait, should I
look for a phone stand?
Wait, I reached Daiso.
Wait, what the
I just reached Daiso out of nowhere.
Wait,
wait. I want to
Is it for
looks like
I think it's Wait, this is like
this is like the back area.
Oh, there's cops. Oh god, there's cops.
Okay, let's go shopping.
I'm scared to keep my tripod over here.
Will someone steal it?
Let's Let's hope so no one steals it,
though.
Okay.
How do you
What the
wait? It's It's closing at 8 though. Ah,
it's closing.
It's closing.
It's closed.
It's closing time. Then I'll just
explore that that area.
What's with the focus, bro?
The camera focus is so bad.
What is What up with the focus?
Okay, focus is auto.
Stabilize.
Ah, there's police people over there.
What is this mall? What is this mall?
Let me recharge since I'm here.
What countries do you visit? No, I can't
visit any countries. I'm stuck in Japan.
I'm stuck in Japan though.
Ah, this is a foot.
Is it okay to film?
>> Just don't do a facial reveal.
It's definitely more interesting than an
I stream really. Yeah, because a
YouTuber is doing it.
Ah,
I have to be careful of reflective area.
I might do myself.
I'll put the blur
uh to like a little bit
so I don't expose myself.
If there's something for cheaper rate, I
might buy.
Oh, cheese. This cheese and stuff,
ain't it?
Oh, these are beers and stuff.
Uh
29.
Ah, it's so expensive. What the hell?
300 yen. No, 400 yen for some crackers
and some mixture and stuff. How much for
noodles?
173 300. What?
Hello.
Uh, it's expensive. This is a little bit
expensive. 16.
Oh, little bit expensive. Oh, wait. You
can get 189.
Wait, how much for rice again? 5 kg is
3,280.
How about 5 kg? 10 kg. Uh, where's 10
kg?
Uh oh. All of these are 5 kg.
Okay. I know a better place rather than
this.
This is the noodles I always eat. Oh,
this is same rate. But wait, it's $429.
Are you going to share with us?
You want some?
I'm not going to buy anything though.
I'm just here focusing. Oh,
look there. This way.
Those are my plans on my
Wow.
Look at this.
What is this?
My white white t-shirt.
I must have gotten when I was in that
for uh cycling forest area.
Uh,
why am I here again? I I don't know.
Why was I here again?
I'll just
also I want to see what what my PC
channel PC is doing. Let me check my um
PC. What's he doing? I'm still watching
Aspen Gold. Okay.
Uh
like there's like a lot of fish
like tuna and meat and everything.
Uh
yeah, there's a lot of meat items. 20%
off.
Ah.
Oh, when it's evening time, they put
offers like that.
Yeah. And the green sticker is an offer
and such.
Yeah, minced meat is here.
What are your thoughts on the re
uh did you find the name? Did you
Did you I don't know the name.
So
pancake.
It's a pancake.
Eight.
Oh, mushrooms and o is that octopus.
Um, square
27.
I mean, I shouldn't raise money. I don't
have much of sushi.
Padillacs.
Why paradox?
Paradillax reminds me of paddle space.
That dwell
app thingy.
How much is this one candy?
That's a lot of people. Why are they
looking at me here? Do I have anything
on my face? No. Is it cuz I'm a
foreigner?
Yeah, but these are 5 kg, right?
Ah, that's a cute lady.
Parallax.
Tell me your thoughts on why did you
name it paradox?
>> Give me your thoughts.
Okay, I'll just leave.
Okay, look at that.
Alex is not a band. I like that name cuz
that's the song I like with the same
name and the meaning makes sense for
that. Then go for it.
My tires are so
Oh I forgot I was able to freeze
people. What the hell? Okay, my tires
are so dusty.
Yeah, it's a good name though. paradox.
You have to check if there's no app with
the same name.
Make it unique though.
Okay, let's go.
before we head off.
Also, Arita, you added the manual
controls now,
the focus and stuff. I did not know
that. I unless I just checked.
Okay,
let me bring some water.
I keep rolling.
Okay, let's go.
I have to take a left.
Right.
What's my charge? 50%. Okay. Uh power
bank 70%. Okay.
Also, Arita, I want to say uh for some
reason uh
uh maybe because of too much load, but
uh my uh when I closed
uh we spoke live
then uh uh I just crossed the red light,
but uh then it it
Maybe the app was too much or something.
When I put my char power bank now, it
was on green power fast charging. And
when I close the Whisper app and the
Google Maps app, it it allowed me to go
uh have the orange the the
green the the
uh charging the super uh super fast
charging.
So I think it's if this is that an
Android thingy do let me know. Okay.
Oh, it's a Right back.
Ah, McDonald's.
Oh, wait. There's a helicopter up there.
Wait, there's a helicopter.
There's a helicopter.
That's a helicopter.
Oh my god. Cool. Cool.
Nothing for Anders.
Uh, no streaming app.
for the
uh
okay
one more thing I want to ask you could
you uh when when I'm adding camera hours
on a slider or toggle uh no on slider
toggle is not uh advanced yet when I'm
Uh when I'm adding a slider uh thingy
for camera, could you add the manual uh
controls too? like um I know you added
zoom and exposure to add focus manual
focus be uh white balance even the uh if
possible the auto
zero make it auto or just put like a
small button to make it auto or
something so I can still have the zero
to 100.
Could you, if possible, could you write
that out?
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh my god, that's a police.
Oh my god. Thank god I did not get
caught that. Thank god I stopped as a
go.
Hi Anagashimas. Thank you.
Now uh
we'll reach
8:30.
Hello
It's blurry again,
isn't it? Is it
Heat.
Oh, I reach Belgium.
Oh, I reached this place.
Uh, this is the one of the branch office
of our right.
I should go there and ask
what which is can I use their SIM card
if it's fast enough for my live streams
and stuff. I should ask them that.
Oh, we found an ramen place.
A soba. It's a soba. It's sobba.
A KFC.
Guess he's
uh
All right.
Hi,
let me read some chat.
Uh,
someone added those features. Yeah.
Yeah. Um,
get a horn hold on cycle. I am on a
Yeah, I'm on tripod. I forgot.
Uh
the best way now I could buy like a
umbrella holder and put the phone there
so you can get like a better view.
This video is more shaky. I should have
a gimbal or something.
Vibration during motion blur.
Hold on.
Heat.
Is that a gym?
That is I think that's an ambulance.
Oh, I'm
Why do they Why drive so slow for an
ambulance? What?
Huh?
If there's an animal then say you're
supposed to go fast.
Why are you driving so slow?
Oh, another one.
It's an actual
actual fire truck.
>> They're crazy.
Wow.
Another fire truck.
>> Oh my god.
Daddy.
Wait, something is happening over there.
That house got on fire or something.
A crazy. That house literally is burning
in fire though.
Wow.
I feel like it's blurry.
Can I check this? Can Can you check the
score? I did saw the number.
Uh the thing is now it's uh
I'm literally stuck with I did the
whisper payment, right?
So uh
I did the whisper payment, right? So I I
am left with $1.
That's the thing.
I'm left with $1 in my bank right now.
I shouldn't have been
waiting.
>> What the is happening?
Is it that high emergency? What the
hell?
Ya, crazy. There's more coming.
How many cops was that? What the hell?
Yo, what?
Wait, Archa, can't you take it from the
whisper payment?
I did. I did do the $3 thing.
Heat.
Oh my god. Heat.
Oh,
can we check out what's happening?
Uh, there's so many cops and police. I
cannot go there.
Thank you, Shadow 7622 for following.
That's good.
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
Oh, Toyota.
Oh, 2 kilometers left. Another
fire truck.
Oh, Toyota.
Wow.
Crazy, man. Crazy.
Heat.
I smell that good firing.
Are those kids playing on the road?
They're dancing on the street. How they
are
dancing on the street
dancing.
Where is it?
The family market.
Where is this?
How how much long? Okay. Three
or two
You make
entertainment and amusement. Welcome to
Monday.
Halal food. Wait, this is a good store.
Wait, where is this?
Halal store is cool. Ah, I reached the
L. What the hell?
What the What time does L close?
What time is it right now? 82, right?
There is Lica.
Okay, let's go.
Go fast.
Oh, what is that? Is that a light house?
A car?
That is cool.
Heat.
What time is that second street clothes?
Oh, this is a restaurant.
Oh, look a dongle.
Okay.
That is
Oh
>> I thought something like that will
happen.
I lost count how many times the camera
fell off.
Okay,
I lost.
Heat. Heat.
Oh, look what the
Am I still live by the way? Can someone
control?
I don't know. Is that
Heat.
Heat up
here.
Okay.
This area is so
Oh, this area is so quiet and
feel like I really need a second phone,
man, to control my stuff.
I can I do have the wrist phone holder.
I can use that to control this uh
paradox in the future only if I have a
second phone.
I just found a good spot.
>> Do you remember the Tanabata vlog?
I did.
I found the water.
You know, let's just get home.
That's priority.
Let's
just get going. That's the ultra main
priority.
Heat. Heat.
Oh, it is like that.
So, we have to take
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
Oh boy.
This area is full of really cool
buildings.
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
in there.
I could go straight
>> actually. I can go straight.
Why is also everywhere?
Ah, there's so much
here.
Let's go to this
stupid.
Yeah, let's stick with this.
Ah,
so far away.
That's a charge.
Okay.
Any moment? No. Green light.
Ah, it's so cold. What's the
temperature?
17°C. What the hell?
It's so cold.
Look at green.
Can I get the
weather is so great. It's so fun. It's
so nice.
I stream for 3 hours.
The stream was real. It's crazy.
Oh boy.
Next time I'm bringing water and my
wireless mic.
Oh boy.
Oh, it's so cold.
It's so cold.
It is so cold now.
Heat. Heat.
Oh boy.
It's so cold out here.
Heat.
It has to speed up. Heat.
Heat up
here.
Heat.
Okay,
I'm on this
Go to the nearby.
There's a park nearby.
I want to stop by there.
Uh today is rest day
on Thursdays or it's Fridays.
Tomorrow day after tomorrow I will be
like walking down from here
coming back from work.
I'll be like coming down from work
and stuff.
along this part
like at 9:30
uh
10 p.m.
moment
like this.
I need my car.
This is where I usually come down to
chill.
So, let's chill for a bit. Okay. Since I
cycle so much,
I'm just going to chill out here.
My usual place.
I have an idea. I can wash my tires if I
go to the other end.
But I'll just do that. Rather doing it
for another video. Actually, I can do it
here.
Yeah. Put a key over here, I guess.
Yeah. So, I go over here
and grab the water and my bottle.
I'll be back in a bit. Okay.
Tell me you did not hear anything.
Okay.
Let me wash my glass.
I'll do the back wheel actually.
Oh, this is such a dumb line.
What the
I should just bring it over here.
I can't believe
Okay, back wheel is done.
And the most hardest part will be the
friend wheel.
Oh, for friendly. I can just watch too.
Uh, how do I do this?
Okay.
Where am I?
Okay, that should do it.
Did you see my face earlier? No. Right.
I hope not.
Super hard to make out what is
happening.
That's so dark.
Oh god.
Okay, I'll wrap up the stream in
five minutes. Four, six minutes. Okay, I
know five minutes. Yeah.
It's going to be nice.
We've been streaming for more than 3
hours.
Okay,
I should lock my scenes.
Hello, welcome.
Okay. Uh,
why is it this color? Let me see if I
can change the camera thingy.
Why is it green?
Exposure white balance.
Shade auto.
Okay.
Hi,
Lex. So,
let's do a small talking stream and then
talk. Well, let's just chat for a bit.
Is this dark?
Yeah.
Let's go to this scene and chat, I
guess.
Holy Lord, it's so
cold. It's 17°
by
K. Today we went on a really fun
adventure, right? We
we went to see the sunset under the
bridge
and we ended up going
literally 10 to 10 kilometers away from
my home.
Uh we literally lo we got lost in
between.
Um what else happened? Yeah, we
literally got lost.
Google Maps betrayed me.
Uh and I ended up reaching
a middle of nowhere, a dead end.
And uh yeah,
overall today was something. And we
ended up cycling all the way
uh like 10 kilome from K like we cycled
through the like highway and stuff.
That was so nice. Today was something we
know.
And
those who were
here,
those who were here, thank you so much.
It means the world to me.
And I hope the stream was
bearable
because we had a lot of issues.
All right, we had a lot of issues with
the stream.
Uh my my I there were times I almost
doxed myself on the stream like the
phone falling down from the tripod.
Uh so I need to buy a good phone holder
it seems.
Uh yeah, I need to buy a good phone
holder.
That way I can like put it
give you guys like a good
uh good uh view.
Yeah,
I feel like uh I need more
stabilization.
It seems even with a phone holder, it
will the cycle will be shaking.
Yeah. So, I'm thinking even if I like
right now today's stream was me putting
the
phone on a tri on a tripod
and like uh bending the tripod legs on
the cycles basket
that worked. That was more stable. But
on bumpy uh terrain
uh like the forest cycling area and
everything uh we noticed that it was b
super uh bumpy to the point that it fell
off even if I even though I tightened
it. Uh so
so I think I'll try to see what I can do
in the future. For now I'll hand go with
this for now. Uh maybe in the future
I'll just buy like an umbrella uh cycle
umbrella holder
arm
and use that uh somehow to with the for
I don't know how that would work but I
need like a clamp
if I'm correct.
I literally need a clamp.
So yeah, I need a clam, bro.
Today was something.
Nah, today was really something.
How was the stream?
I I dropped a 1014
video and so much audio. Yeah. Thingy.
Wow.
I dropped a lot of frames.
Conjunction.
So, go.
Was there any errors? No errors. That's
a good improvement. We had zero errors.
Crazy.
First time even seeing that.
We had zero errors for today's stream.
crazy though.
Yeah, today was really fun.
Thank you everyone who came by.
It means a lot.
We were cycling a lot today.
Today was
crazy, honestly.
Yeah, today was so crazy.
It gets blurry when I move. That's what
I noticed.
It gets blurry when I move a lot.
What happened in the beginning of the
stream though?
Wait,
I don't see the beginning of the frame.
I thought I did a beginning of the
stream. What the hell?
YouTube, did you lose my stuff?
I don't know. Well, let's thank everyone
who came by today. We've been streaming
for
I I'm I'm sure it's not 1 hour 38
minutes. It's more than that. It's 3
hour 40 minutes.
All the people who came by today are
let's see Mikasuki Yuran thank you for
coming by and good luck with the
rebranding Dio Parallax can't wait for
the new rebrand of the app I'm using for
live streaming and all the new features
you're going to add and all the bug
fixes. I'm excited for that. Thank you
for coming. Goji board son Rad Radido
Radid Radit official son. Thank you for
coming and talking with interacting with
me and welcome to the constellers.
Thank you for interacting me interacting
with me from kick. Thank you. Then Kali
son thank you for coming by. Kunadasan
thank you for coming by
and uh Dealan thank you for coming by.
Why not have TTS in your ear? Uh,
I have to wait till
uh, Paradax adds a browser source
feature
or something. I have to check if I don't
know if you hear the so, but I have to
check if speaker bot
uh, from streamerbot, right? Streamabots
another thing uh uh speaker board I
don't know if I can um make speaker
board
give me text to speech stuff and I send
it over over the internet
uh and uh I can
uh hear it through
uh manifold
or something. Hm. That's a good idea
though. I'm not sure that's a good idea.
I have to look at that. Yeah, I have to
check that uh text speech stuff. Yeah,
text speech is better now. That way I
can read know who what are the chats uh
being uh told and stuff. I can hear
rather than reading and stop stopping
the cycle and reading during cycling
streams. I can listen to everything,
right? Every kind of chat.
Um,
do you know Latin?
Uh, then, uh, who else? Uh,
came by Shadow 7622. Thank you for the
follow on Twitch. Thank you so much.
Uh,
I can't read your name. I believe your
name is Russian. Thank you for coming
by. Long time no see.
You're streaming even now. Yeah, I'm
going to end Konada. Hello. Hello.
Petition to update the clip leaderboard
reset timer to at least one week. Wait,
what is a clip leaderboard?
Wait, there's a clip leaderboard.
Okay, I'm going to make it like one uh
more than one week. one month or
something. I don't have anyone to uh who
would clip me often. No. So, yeah,
that's one thing.
But I would appreciate it if you could
clip me more so I can make some YouTube
shots out of it or something or upload
it to YouTube at least, I guess. I don't
know.
Uh
yeah, every clip you can edit the clip
and add changes.
like uh there's there's going to be
captions can make the vertical format or
something. I think I can do it. Stream
broadcaster can do it. Not sure. I'm
being selfish for But you got a number
one clipping badge though.
Yeah. You got the number one clipping
badge. I just noticed it right now.
Congratulations.
I got a number one badge. It's a guy.
But yeah, how was today's stream? What
do you guys think?
Today we went on an adventure. No,
we really really did go on an adventure
today.
That was crazy.
Ah, it's so cold.
Oh, we really did go on an adventure.
That was so kind.
Oh god,
I'm wearing just a t-shirt.
Ah, so it's so cold as I
should think about what I could do to
improve these uh higher streams
especially cycling streams. I can now do
cycling streams, right? Uh the thing is
I cannot input like an external camera
yet. I need proper hardware for it as in
I need the camera itself. Plus, I need
to find a Raspberry Pi or a Orange Pi
with 4GB at least.
Uh,
so I can uh encode the video feed from a
action camera or a DSLR camera or like a
normal camera and then
um send it to my phone via manifold or
something and uh stream from my phone or
something. I feel like I need like a
second phone so I can control and rehat
or something. I don't know. There's so
many ideas I could experiment with, but
I I'm out of money. I'm broke and I
can't do much. I can only use what I
have right now. I'll try to fix stuff, I
guess. But one of the things I'm
thinking of investing on in the future
for cycle stream frames is I'm thinking
of buying like an umbrella thingy.
Uh,
I was under the bridge. We went cycling.
I was lost in a forest
uh on a cycling area.
Google
bridge. What is the Japanese of bridge
again? Bridge.
Mity.
foreign.
like
Tripod.
Delete.
So
uh
nobody show
Ianoch.
coin.
Yeah, today was so fun, bro. I got lost
here and there, but
yeah,
it it was just supposed to be us looking
at the sunset and talking. I ended up
making it a cycling adventure stream.
You can try an IRL horror stream
sometime.
I I hate horror.
Sorry. Uh um English. Sorry. This month
is Halloween, right? So, I'm supposed to
do a few horror streams.
So, I have to like do it on Saturday or
Sunday. This Saturday, Sunday. Probably
in the afternoon or morning
I'll do some horror streams.
Yeah, there are some games I have to
finish.
So yeah,
but yeah, I don't know. Game game game
PC stream
PC.
But yeah, let's wrap up. It's 9:15.
Uh, let's let's wrap up.
I'll uh stream again tomorrow.
Tomorrow is Thursday, right? I don't
have work Thursday. So, uh tomorrow as
well. Um sunset is at like 5:00 p.m. I'm
not sure if I'm going to do another
adventure thingy like this. Maybe I'll
do a desktop stream tomorrow.
I don't know. I did two IRL streams,
right?
Uh so yeah.
Hi, have a good one everyone. I'll go
uh go to my dometry and I'll go rest up,
eat good food, eat something
and
um yeah, do I'll do a lot of things. I
have to do my homework. Ah god, there's
homework.
So yeah, have a good one everyone.
Also, what's my PC doing? Like before I
end, let me doing PC.
Uh, what's my PC doing?
I'm still watching Asmin Gold.
I'm still watching Asmin Gold. Okay.
Hi Ana. Bye-bye everyone.
Wait, I can I can sketch this. What the
um
bye
bye-bye. What's going to